Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jessica-hanguyen (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Brand Design Communication Print Design

Languages

English Vietnamese

Ha Nguyen

UI/UX Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I am a UI/UX Designer with over 5 years of experience specializing in user experience design. I have had the opportunity to work on diverse projects, ranging from mobile applications to web platforms. My skills include creating creative and efficient user interface designs, ensuring optimized and user-friendly experiences. I am proficient in design tools such as Adobe XD, Sketch, and Figma to create designs from concept to final product. Additionally, I prioritize user feedback and analytics data to iterate and improve products.

Experience

Kyanon Digital
UI/ UX Designer
October 2021 - Present (3 years 6 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

J&T Express Vietnam
UI/ UX Designer
April 2021 - September 2021 (6 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

I redesigned UI/ UX and refreshed some internal system features like OA (Office Automatic), BI...

Siêu Thị Nhật Bản Japana UI/ UX Designer May 2020 - February 2021 (10 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Together with Business analyst created admin portal: CMS, ERP, CRM. Design layout e-commerce website.

Blockdev Company Ltd.
UI Designer
March 2019 - April 2020 (1 year 2 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Design layout website, mobile application, admin portal for blockchain project.

TECHLOVE Solution Software Company Limited UI Designer
October 2015 - March 2019 (3 years 6 months)

Hochiminh City, VietNam

Design layout website, mobile application for Restaurant, Health application, Jobs application, Transfer money

Buoc Chan Viet
Graphic Designer
September 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 1 month)
Hochiminh City, Vietnam

Giải Pháp Toàn Cầu (Modial solution) Graphic Designer September 2013 - June 2014 (10 months) Hochiminh City, VietNam

Education

College SaiGonACT

bachelor of Science in Graphic Design, Graphic Design · (2009 - 2012)